Arthur J. Cain Papers 1945-1988 Mss.Ms.Coll.63
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1945-1988; 33 boxes; 16.25 linear feet
  - Cowie, Robert Hulin, 2 folders (Box Series I-5)
    - Folder #1, 1980-1984 (Box Series I-5)
    - Folder #2, 1985-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-5)
  - Cox, Brian, 1977 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cox, C. Barry, 1976-1977 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cox, R.J., 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cracraft, Joel, 1972-1975 (Box Series I-5)
  - Crane, P.S., 1964 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cranwell, Michael P., 1987 (Box Series I-5)
  - Crawford, Martin d'A., 1972 (Box Series I-5)
  - Crawshay-Williams, Rupert, 1965 (Box Series I-5)
  - Creed, Edwin Robert, 1965-1979 (Box Series I-6)
    Bellamy, Denis
    Lees, David
  - Crebbin, C., 1981 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crisci, J.V., 1977; 1981 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crisp, Dennis J., 1981 (Box Series I-6)
  - Croft, L.R., 1986 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crompton, A.W., 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crook, John H., 1972-1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crook, Steve J., 1974-1981 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cross, James E., 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crothers, John H., 1977-1985 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crowther, Wilma, 1985; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Crozier, Ross H., 1971-1983 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cullen, J. Mike, 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cummins, E.A., 1965-1966 (Box Series I-6)
  - Currey, John D, 2 folders (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder #1, 1963-1980 (Box Series I-6)
      Frome, Joy
      Roberts, Michael B.V.
    - Folder #2, 1981-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Curtis, Chris F., 1983 (Box Series I-6)
  - Curtis, Simon E.G., 1972-1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cushing, P.H., 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Dalingwater, John, 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Dan, Victor, 1978 (Box Series I-6)
  - Dance, S. Peter, 1968-1986; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Daniels, Charles M., 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Daniels, David, 1983 (Box Series I-6)
  - D'Arcy Thomson, Ruth, 1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, Arthur B., 1965 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, David, 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, D.R., 1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, Douglas M., 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, E.B., 1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, J.N., 1962; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, John B., 1981-1985; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, Keith C., 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, Mick, n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, P. Spencer, 1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, Robert S., 1986-1987; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, Stella M., 1977-1988 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davies, Stephen J.J.F., 1975-1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davis, George Morgan, 4 folders (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder #1, 1974-1976 (Box Series I-6)
      Davis, K. Elaine Hoagland
    - Folder #2, 1977-1979 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder #3, 1980-1983 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder #4, 1984-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Davis, Stephen, 1984-1985 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davy, Jeremy, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dawes, J.A., 1972-1977 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dawkins, Richard, 1976-1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dawson, Noel J., 1968 (Box Series I-7)
  - Day, Alan, 1986 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dayrit, Fernando G., 1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - de Bartolomé, J.F.M., 1976 (Box Series I-7)
  - Deblock, F. René, 1964-1977 (Box Series I-7)
  - Deisler, Jane E., n.d. (Box Series I-7)
  - de Lara, Maria Victoria, 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - de Matos, R.M. Albuquerque, 1979; 1986 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dennell, Ralph, 1964-1969 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dennis, Geoff F.C., 1954; 1960 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dennis, Roger L.H., 1978-1981 (Box Series I-7)
  - Derstler, Kraig, 1977 (Box Series I-7)
  - de Ruiter, Leen, 1962 (Box Series I-7)
  - De Smet, W.H.O., 1987 (Box Series I-7)
  - Devlin, Susan, 1977 (Box Series I-7)
  - Diamond, A.W., 1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - Diamond, Jared M., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-7)
  - Díaz-Piferrer, M., 1976-1977 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dickinson, Paul S., n.d. (Box Series I-7)
  - Diver, Cyril, 1968-1971 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dixon, R. Michael, 1984 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dobzhansky, Theodosius (Box Series I-7)
    -See Ser.I, Provine, William B.
  - Dodd, James M., 1973-1980 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dommée, Bertrand, 1974-1978 (Box Series I-7)
    Jury, Stephen L.
    Sheppard, Philip M.
  - Donagho, Walter R. (Box Series I-7)
    -See Ser.I, Galbraith, Ian C.J.
  - Dormer, K.J., 1968 (Box Series I-7)
  - Douglas, Ann. Folder #1, 1959-1971 (Box Series I-7)
  - Douglas, Ann. Folder #2, 1972-1977 (Box Series I-7)
  - Doumudj, [?], 1979 (Box Series I-7)
  - Doust, J.N. Lovett, 1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dover, Gabriel A., 1983-1984 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dowdeswell, W.H., 1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - Downes, Mary, 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Driver, P.M., 1982 (Box Series I-7)
  - Drozdowski, Arnold, 1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dubock, Adrian C., 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - Ducker, J.T., 1958 (Box Series I-7)
  - Duke, James A., 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dunbar, Robin, 1967-1968; n.d. (Box Series I-7)
  - Duncan, Chris, 1976 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dundee, Dee S., 1978-1979 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dunkley, J.M., 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dunn, Euan K., 1973 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dussart, Georges B.J., 1986 (Box Series I-7)
  - Eagar, R. Michael C., 1977-1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - Easteal, Simon, 1983 (Box Series I-7)
  - Eddington, John, 1971 (Box Series I-7)
  - Edmonds, J.M., 1976 (Box Series I-7)
  - Edmondson, W.T. (Box Series I-7)
    -See Ser.I, Mayr, Ernst
  - Edmunds, Malcolm, 1968-1986 (Box Series I-7)
  - Edwards, Pat, 1985 (Box Series I-7)
  - Edwards, Roy L., 1953 (Box Series I-7)
  - Ekis, Ginter, 1964; 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Ellis, David, 1982-1983 (Box Series I-7)
  - Else, George R., 1983 (Box Series I-7)
  - Emberton, Kenneth C., 1983-1986; n.d. (Box Series I-7)
  - Emmel, Thomas C., 1981 (Box Series I-7)
  - Emmerson, John, 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Emmett, H.E.G., 1964; 1978 (Box Series I-7)
  - Endler, John A, 2 folders (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder #1, 1975-1982 (Box Series I-8)
      Endler, Tracey
    - Folder #2, 1983-1986; n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Endler, Tracey (Box Series I-8)
    -See Ser.I, Endler, John A.
  - Eriksson, Aldur W., 1985 (Box Series I-8)
  - Estill, Frederica, 1959 (Box Series I-8)
  - Evans, M. Elyn G., 1972 (Box Series I-8)
  - Evans, John G., 1971-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Evans, Nicholas John, 1972-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Evans, Peter, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eversham, Brian, 1985-1986 (Box Series I-8)
    Kermack, Doris M.
  - Ewens, Warren, 1978 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ewers, William Hector, 1966-1968 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fa, John Manuel, 1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fairbrother, J.R.F., 1968 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fairhurst, Colin, 1964; 1971 (Box Series I-8)
  - Falconer, Douglas S., 1972-1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Faller-Fritsch, Robert, 1974-1980 (Box Series I-8)
  - Farmer, Anthony S., 1972 (Box Series I-8)
  - Farrelly, Peter J., 1976 (Box Series I-8)
  - Farrer-Brown, Leslie, 1958-1961 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fay, D.W.B., 1966 (Box Series I-8)
  - Feare, Chris J., 1973 (Box Series I-8)
  - Feldman, Anne, 1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - Feldman, Anthony, 1971 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ferguson, Harry, 1976 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ferry, Georgina, 1979 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fifield, R.J., 1971-1978 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fincham, J.R.S., 1974-1978 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fincham, Tony, 1982 (Box Series I-8)
  - Findley, John, 1970 (Box Series I-8)
  - Finlayson, J. Clive, 1973-1979 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fish, John, 1975; 1980 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fisher, Clem, 1986 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fisher, Roderick C., 1987 (Box Series I-8)
  - Flinn, A.M., 1982 (Box Series I-8)
  - Flinn, D., 1980 (Box Series I-8)
  - Foden, K., 1964 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fogan, Marjorie, 1970 (Box Series I-8)
  - Follett, Brian K., 1980 (Box Series I-8)
  - Foote, Michael J., 1985 (Box Series I-8)
  - Foppa, R. (Box Series I-8)
  - Forbes-Watson, A.D., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ford, E.B. [Henry], 1964-1986; n.d. (Box Series I-9)
  - Ford, Hugh A., 1971-1980; n.d. (Box Series I-9)
  - Forgan, Sophie, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-9)
  - Francis, Cyril, 1960 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fraser, [?], 1959 (Box Series I-9)
  - Freeman, Peter, 1986 (Box Series I-9)
  - Freeman, Richard B., 1966-1972 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fresco-Corbu, Roger, 1979 (Box Series I-9)
  - Frey, David G., 1953 (Box Series I-9)
  - Friday, Adrian, 1980 (Box Series I-9)
  - Friston, M.H., 1982 (Box Series I-9)
  - Frome, Joy, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser.I, Currey, John D.
  - Frost, B.W., 1975 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fry, Chilan H., 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fry, William G., 1963-1974 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fuller, Jim, 1959; n.d. (Box Series I-9)
  - Fullington, Richard W., 1984 (Box Series I-9)
  - Furnell, Norman, 1976 (Box Series I-9)
  - Furniss, R., 1970 (Box Series I-9)
  - Futuyma, Douglas J., 1981 (Box Series I-9)
    Williamson, P.G.
  - Gabbutt, P.D., 1964 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gable, Michael, 1977 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gaillard, J.M., 1975 (Box Series I-9)
  - Galbraith, Ian C.J., 1955-1981 (Box Series I-9)
    Donagho, Walter R.
    Secker, H.L.
    -See also Oversized
  - Galbraith, Ian C.J., 27 Mar. 1956 (Box Series I-33)
    Enclosure (Oversize)
  - Galloway, John John Woodhead, 1984-1985 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gandy, N.J., 1982 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gans, Carl, 1966 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gardner, R.L., 1975 (Box Series I-9)
  - Garfoot, Margaret E., 1972 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gartside, D.W., 1976 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gaskin, David E., 1972-1980 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gates, Simon M.G., 1976-1985 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gayre, R., 1960-1961 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ghilarov, Mercury S., 1985 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ghiselin, Michael T., 1975-1989 (Box Series I-9)
  - Giachardi, D.J., 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gibb, John A., 1953-1980 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gibby, Michael, 1971-1972; n.d. (Box Series I-9)
  - Gibson, I., 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gibson, Raymond, 1986 (Box Series I-9)
  - Giles, Nick, 1978 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gill, A., 1972 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gill, Frank B., 1975 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gill, Peter, 1973-1986 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gillman, John, 1976-1978 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gillman, R. J., 1952 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gilmour, John S.L., 1955-1964 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gismann, Anne, 1980 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gittenberger, Edmund, 1979-1988 (Box Series I-10)
  - Giusti, Folco, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-10)
  - Glass, Chris W., 1986-1987 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gleaves, T., 1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - Glover, Tim D., 1970-1983 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gompertz, Terry, 1968 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goodall, Alan G. Folder #1, 1969-1972 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goodall, Alan G. Folder #2, 1973-1979; n.d. (Box Series I-10)
  - Goodfriend, Glenn A., 1977-1984; n.d. (Box Series I-10)
  - Goodhart, Charles B., 1962-1974 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goodwin, Brian, 1972-1974 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goormaghtigh, John, 1984 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gordon, Hopeton Leopold Alexander, 1975-1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gosliner, Terry M., 1983-1985 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gotto, V., 1981 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gould, Stephen Jay, 1978-1980 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goulden, Clyde E., 1976-1977; n.d. (Box Series I-10)
  - Gouyon, Pierre-Henri, 1984-1986 (Box Series I-10)
  - Grady, Th. C., 1968 (Box Series I-10)
  - Graetz, Sarah J. (Box Series I-10)
    -See Ser.I, Gregg, Alan T.
  - Graham, Alistair, 1970-1975 (Box Series I-10)
  - Graham, W.S., 1979 (Box Series I-10)
  - Grahame, John, 1987 (Box Series I-10)
  - Grant, Peter, 1971-1979 (Box Series I-10)
  - Green, Chris H., 1981 (Box Series I-10)
  - Green, Malcolm, 1970 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greene, John C., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greenslade, P.J.M., 1968 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greenwood, E.F., 1977 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greenwood, Jeremy John Denis, 2 folders (Box Series I-10)
    - Folder #1, 1963-1971 (Box Series I-10)
      -See also Ser.I, Armstrong, Roy
    - Folder #2, 1972-1987; n.d. (Box Series I-10)
  - Greenwood, Julian, 1973-1985 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greenwood, P.H., 1968-1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greenwood, Paul J., 1979 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greer, Terry, 1977; 1980 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gregg, Alan T., 1965-1977; n.d. (Box Series I-10)
    Graetz, Sarah J.
  - Gregory, Rod. A., 1987 (Box Series I-10)
  - Griffiths, D.A., 1977 (Box Series I-10)
  - Grimwade, A.M., 1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gross, Harm P, 2 folders (Box Series I-11)
    - Folder #1, 1976-1977 (Box Series I-11)
    - Folder #2, 1978-1980 (Box Series I-11)
  - Grossu, A.V., 1982 (Box Series I-11)
  - Grubb, P.J. (Box Series I-11)
    -See Ser.I, Harper, G.H.
  - Grüneberg, H., 1976 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gruson, Edward S., 1974 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gundrum, Lois E., 1978 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gurdon, John B., 1977 (Box Series I-11)
  - Guthrie, D.M., 1975 (Box Series I-11)
    -See also Ser.I, Bailey, Stuart E.R.
  - Haakonssen, Lis, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hadfield, Michael G., 1981-1982 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hagen, D[on] W., 1977-1978 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hair, Paul E.H., 1984-1985 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hale, William G., 1967-1981; n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Halkka, O[lli], 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, B. Pat, 1966-1974 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, W.B., 1968 (Box Series I-11)
  - Halstead, L. Beverly, 1979-1985 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hamilton, David F., 1980-1981 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hamilton, Paul V., 1981 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hancock, E.G., 1977 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanford, Paul, 1971; n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Hannaford, Celia J., 1975-1984; n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanson, J., 1967 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanson, L., 1983 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harasewych, Jerry, 1977 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harding, John P., 1963-1964 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardstaff, Malcolm, 1979-1984; n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardwick, W.H., 1965 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardy, Alister C., 1957-1980 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardy, David, 1983-1984 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harel, M. (Box Series I-11)
    -See Ser.I, Levi, Claude
  - Harley, J.L., 1971-1972 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harper, G.H., 1963-1967 (Box Series I-11)
    Coombe, David
    Grubb, P.J.
  - Harper, John L., 1972 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, N.J.T., 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harrison, Geoffrey Ainsworth, 1953-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Harrison, R.G., 1980-1983 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harry, Owen G., 1984 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hartley, Colin, 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hartnoll, Richard, 1974; 1986 (Box Series I-12)
  - Harvey, Andrew, 1978 (Box Series I-12)
  - Harvey, Paul, 1968-1986 (Box Series I-12)
    Sheppard, P.M.
  - Harwood, David, 1984 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hawkes, Jack G., 1968; 1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hawkes, N.J., 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hawkins, Stephen J., 1977; 1988 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hawksworth, D.L., 1975-1977 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hawton, Hector, 1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hayami, Itaru, 1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hazzledine, P.M., 1981-1982 (Box Series I-12)
  - Head, R., 1973; 1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heal, Jon, 1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heath, David J., 1972-1975; n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Hécaen, H., 1973 (Box Series I-12)
    -See also Ser.I, von Cranach, Mario
  - Hecht, Max K., 1969 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hedgecock, Dennis, 1983 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heller, Joseph, 2 folders (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #1, 1972-1977 (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #2, 1978-1987; n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Helm, Paul, 1980 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hemmen, G.E., 1960-1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henderson, Andrew E., 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henderson, Ian F., 1983 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henty, Cliff J., 1971-1980 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heppell, David, 1986 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heppleston, Paul B., 1970-1972; n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Hereward, Vanora, 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hershler, Robert, 1976-1978 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heslop-Harrison, Jack, 1946-1975; n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Hewitt, Godfrey M., 1968-1988 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heywood, Vernon H., 1971-1986 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hibbert, Alan, n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Higgins, Lionel G., 1982-1983 (Box Series I-12)
  - High, Olga Bayliss, 1982 (Box Series I-12)
  - Higham, Thomas, 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hill, John Edwards, 1954 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hill, Kenneth, 1959 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hillman, L.J., 1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hinchliffe, Richard, 1975-1978 (Box Series I-12)
    Hollingworth, Charles
  - Hinde, Robert A., 1970 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hindle, E., 1965-1966 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hines, Andrew, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hitchcock, Warren, 1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hoagland, K. Elaine, 1975-1987 (Box Series I-12)
    -See also Ser.I, Davis, George Morgan
  - Hobbs, G.H., 1954 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hogan, G.F.P., 1955 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hohenadel, Marlene S., 1977 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holliday, A.K., 1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holliday, Fred G.T., 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hollingworth, Charles, 1977 (Box Series I-12)
    -See also Ser.I, Hinchliffe, Richard
  - Holloway, Jeremy, 1970-1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holyoak, David, 1978-1981 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hooper, David, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hoover, Peter R., 1984 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hopton, Elaine V., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hornblower, Robert, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-12)
  - Horsley, David, 1973 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hosie, Robin, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-12)
  - House, Michael R., 1977-1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Howells, J.D., 1974-1978; n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Howgate, Michael, 1982 (Box Series I-12)
  - Howlett, Rory J., 1984 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hubbard, Dorothy J., 1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hubbard, S., 1986 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hubricht, Leslie, 1985 (Box Series I-13)
  - Huby, Pamela, 1988 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hudman, Patric J., 1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hudson, P.J., 1980; n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Hudson, Roger, 1970 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hugh-Jones, David, n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Hughes, George M., 1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hughes, N.F., 1971 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hughes, Roger, 1974-1981 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hull, David L., 1965 (Box Series I-13)
  - Humphreys, John, 1977-1981 (Box Series I-13)
  - Humphries, David A., 1981-1983 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hunt, David, 1987-1988 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hunt, John, 1975-1982 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hunt, Stephen, 1981 (Box Series I-13)
  - Huntingford, Felicity, 1979 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hurd, Paul D., 1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Husain, Kazi Zaker, 1979-1983 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hussain, K.M.Z., 1959 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hutchinson, John, 1984-1985 (Box Series I-13)
  - Huxley, Andrew, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-13)
  - Huxley, Julian S., 1956-1974; 2 folders (Box Series I-13)
    Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Darwin, Charles; Evolution; Fellowships, assistantships; Genetics -- Birds; Genetics -- Snails; Genetics of plants; Glass, Bentley; Human genetics; Kirkaldy, J. S.; Lectures, public speaking; Mayr, Ernst; Mendel, Gregor; Oxford University; Population, demography; Publication; Requests for reprints; Research support; Scientific refugees; Sheppard, Philip M.; Teilhard de Chardin, Pierre; Travel -- Africa; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Zoology; Zoology -- Africa; Zoology -- Classification
    - Folder #1, 1956-1965 (Box Series I-13)
      Kirkaldy, J.S.
    - Folder #2, 1966-1974; n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Hwang, S.J., 1970 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hyett, Marvin, 1975-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Idnani, Saroj G., 1974 (Box Series I-13)
  - Impey, Oliver R., 1971 (Box Series I-13)
  - Inglis, W. Grant, 1987 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ingram, David C., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ingram, Philippa, 1978 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jacobs, Paul, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jacobs, Theo, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jacobsen, Vogg H., 1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jacobson, M.K., 1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - James, Matt, 1983 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jamieson, Alan, 1967 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jamieson, Barrie, 1976 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jarman, Peter J, 2 folders (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #1, 1961-1967 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #2, 1968-1984; n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Jarman, Peter J., 25 Oct. 1966 (Box Series I-33)
    Maps (Oversize)
  - Jeffery, Richard C.V., 1976-1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jenkins, Malcolm, 1978-1979 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jennings, David H., 1975 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jessop, Adrienne, 1980 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jewell, Peter J., 1978-1982 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jewsbury, John, 1986; n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Jinks, John L., 1972-1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - John, Barney, 1983 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johns, David L., 1963-1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Andrew P.I., 1983-1984 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Brian, 1977-1978; n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Helen A., 1980-1986 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Michael S., 1975; 1977-1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jolicoeur, Pierre, n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Jollands, Peter, 1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jollett, Anthony J., 1969 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jolliffe, C., 1963-1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, Bryn M., 1980-1981 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, Carol, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, D.H., 1971 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, David, 1971-1986 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, Eric, 1972; 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, H.D., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, J. Christopher, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, J. Steve, 1969-1987 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, Steve J., 3 Feb. 1981 (Box Series I-33)
    Enclosures (Oversize)
  - Jones, Jack W., 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, Jeff, 1984 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, Kevin P., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jordan, Dominic, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Joysey, Ken A., 1980-1987 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jury, Stephen L. (Box Series I-14)
    -See Ser.I, Dommée, Bertrand
  - Karsholt, Ole, 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kearsey, Michael J., 1982 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keast, Allen, 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keay, R.W.J., 1964 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keller, E.C., 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kelley, Aileen, 1981 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kelley, T., 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kennedy, Clive R., 1975-1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kermack, Doris M. (Box Series I-14)
    -See Ser.I, Eversham, Brian
  - Kerney, Michael P., 1977-1984 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kerrich, Geoffrey J., 1954-1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kershaw, W[illiam] E., 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kettlewell, H.B.D., 1964-1972; n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Key, Ken H.L., 1985 (Box Series I-14)
  - Khanzode, Vibhavari R., 1967-1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Khokhutkin, Igor Moiseevith, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kikkawa, Jiro, 1983 (Box Series I-14)
  - Killick, H.J., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, [?], 1958 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, Anthony S., 1972-1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, J.M.B., 1958 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, P.E., 1971-1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, Sue, 1986-1987 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, Wayne, 1983 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kinnock, Neil, 1987 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kiriakou, C.P., 1982-1983 (Box Series I-14)
    Bambos
  - Kirk, R., 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kirkaldy, J.S. (Box Series I-14)
    -See Ser.I, Huxley, Julian S.
  - Kirwan, L.P., 1959-1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kitching, R., 1983 (Box Series I-14)
  - Klaffke, Oliver, 1987 (Box Series I-14)
  - Klauber, Ruth, 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Klimetzek, Dietrich, 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knight, Andrew J., 1986; n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Knox, Alan G., 1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knudsen, J., 1977-1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kohn, A.J., 1983 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kondratas, Ramunas, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kool, Silvard, 1981; n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Korn, M. Eric, 1979-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Kottler, Malcolm, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kraemer, L. Russert, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kraeuter, John N., 1986 (Box Series I-14)
  - Krebs, John R., 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Krimbas, Costas B., 1977-1987; n.d.; 21.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)